



ABOUT ME

Experienced secretary field more than 5 years in the foreign affairs related company/ organization with demonstrated an ability to keep track of everything from deadlines to essential files, effectively manage an executive schedule, coordinate with high-levelmanagement personal assistant with proper manner and protocol as well. Strong detailedoriented professional with a role focused in the full pack of secretarial and other tasks assigned. Self- initiative. Understanding professional standards/company's regulations with proven track record of reliability and determination.

O CAREER OBJECTIVES

Seeking for the opportunity to work with company/ organization where I can improve work practices and utilize skills in multifaceted levels such as organizational communication skills, initiative and moving forwards, being a team player, coping with stress and working under pressure, problem solving skills, flexibility and adaptability, and professionalism to contribute profitability, business growth, and company success.



















Star Gazing

Music

Methiya Mueangmeesap

Executive Secretary



+668 2717 8288



m.methiya@hotmail.com





Bangkok, Thailand Methiya Mueangmeesap



---- EDUCATION ------

2011 - 2015 SILPAKORN UNIVERSITY

> Bachelor of Arts (English, Chinese) GPA 3.23 (Second class honour)

CHONKANYANUKOON SCHOOL 2008 - 2010

Maths and Science Programme

2005 - 2007 English Programme



WORK EXPERIENCE -----

The Eastern Economic Corridor Office of Thailand 2019 - 2022 **International Affairs Coordinator** (Contract ended)

(Executive Secretary to Deputy Secretary General)

2017 - 2019 The Siam Commercial Bank

(Contract ended) Secretary to Senior Vice President





Kumiai Chemica Industry Co., Ltd. 2016 - 2017

Secretary to Manager (Japanese)

2015 - 2016 The Ministry of Foreign Affairs

Research and Manage Information Staff

2014 - 2014The Ministry of Foreign Affairs

Trainee (March 2014 - June 2014)



SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Computer Literacy

Basic:





Intermediate:



Engine









Languages

Proficient:

Thai: Native

English: Proficient (TOEIC 835)

Chinese: Basic

Licesce: Valid driving license



· — · — · REFERENCES — · — · — · — · — ·

MS. CHAWANIS CHAWANAWONG

Counsellor, The Ministry of Foreign Affairs Contact: +668 9404 0703

MS.CHULEEPORN AMORNJITRANONT

SVP, The Siam Commercial Bank Contact: +669 5997 9516

MR. HIRAN RUJIRAWIROTE

Former Deputy Director, EEC Contact: +668 7600 1891